var jsonGeneral = `{
		"id": 100,
		"title": "General",
		"clues_count": 20,
		"clues": [{
				"id": 1000,
				"answer": "Green",
				"question": "A term that describes a horse with very little training",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1001,
				"answer": "Bray",
				"question": "The sound a donkey makes",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1002,
				"answer": "Quick release",
				"question": "The type of knot used when tying up a horse",
				"value": 300,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1003,
				"answer": "32",
				"question": "Horses have this many pairs of chromosomes",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1004,
				"answer": "Ration",
				"question": "The entire feed allowed an animal during a 24 hour period",
				"value": 500,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1005,
				"answer": "Appointments",
				"question": "The term for clothing, tack, and equipment used in show riding",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1006,
				"answer": "Hippology",
				"question": "The term used for the study of the horse",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1007,
				"answer": "Get",
				"question": "The progeny of a stallion",
				"value": 600,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1008,
				"answer": "Grade",
				"question": "A term used for an unregistered horse of uncertain ancestry",
				"value": 800,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1009,
				"answer": "Hind",
				"question": "Which feet grow faster, hind or front",
				"value": 1000,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1010,
				"answer": "Sire",
				"question": "The gender of the foal is determined by this parent",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1011,
				"answer": "Cow hocked",
				"question": "A term for hocks that are closer together than normal",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1012,
				"answer": "TPR",
				"question": "An acronym for temperature, pulse, and respiration",
				"value": 600,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1013,
				"answer": "Blemish",
				"question": "A mark or deformity that is unattractive but does not affect a horse's usefulness",
				"value": 800,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1014,
				"answer": "Carrier",
				"question": "A term for an animal that can shed disease causing organisms",
				"value": 1000,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1015,
				"answer": "Unsoundness",
				"question": "A defect that affects the serviceability of a horse",
				"value": 200,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1016,
				"answer": "Gymkhana",
				"question": "A series of games on horseback",
				"value": 400,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1017,
				"answer": "Confirmation",
				"question": "A term used to describe the physical appearance of a animal due to the muscling, balance, and structural smoothness of a horse",
				"value": 800,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1018,
				"answer": "Farrier",
				"question": "A person that shoes horses",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1019,
				"answer": "Noseband",
				"question": "Another name for a cavesson",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1020,
				"answer": "10 gallons",
				"question": "The average dialy water intake of a mature 1000 pound horse",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1021,
				"answer": "Hard mouthed",
				"question": "A term that refers to a horse that is not responsive to the bit",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1022,
				"answer": "Tandem hitch",
				"question": "A term that describes a pair of horses hitched together one in front of the other when driving",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1023,
				"answer": "Cribbing",
				"question": "A term that describes biting or setting the teeth against an object while sucking in air",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1024,
				"answer": "Bridle",
				"question": "The headpiece that includes the bit and other accessories used for control during riding or driving",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1025,
				"answer": "Grazing",
				"question": "When a horse consumes standing vegetation",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1026,
				"answer": "Leaves",
				"question": "The most nutritious part of the hay",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1027,
				"answer": "Bedding",
				"question": "The term for the material used to cover the stall floor that provides comfort and absorbs moisture",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1028,
				"answer": "Left",
				"question": "The hand you should use to carry the halter when you are preparing to catch a horse",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1029,
				"answer": "Curry Comb",
				"question": "The brush that should not be used on the face and legs when grooming.",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1030,
				"answer": "Left",
				"question": "The side you should mount a horse from",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1031,
				"answer": "Shank",
				"question": "In reference to western bits, it is the name for the portion of the cheek of the bit from the mouthpiece down to the reins?",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1032,
				"answer": "Pecking order",
				"question": "The common name for the dominance hierarchy or social order exhibited by a group of horses",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1033,
				"answer": "Dominant",
				"question": "The term for the horse at the top of the pecking order",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1034,
				"answer": "Bobtail",
				"question": "The term for a horse with a short or docked tail",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1035,
				"answer": "70",
				"question": "The percent of of water that makes up horses total body weight",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1036,
				"answer": "Unicorn hitch",
				"question": "Name for a hitch with two horses hitched as a pair and a third horse hitched in front of them",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1037,
				"answer": "Kentucky Derby",
				"question": "The Triple Crown is a series of Thoroughbred races. This the first race of the series",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1038,
				"answer": "Big Red",
				"question": "Man of War and Secretariat were famous Thoroughbred race horses that were the same color and had the same nickname. What was the nickname?",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			},{
				"id": 1039,
				"answer": "Draft",
				"question": "This type of horse were used the most to farm the land and move goods to the population centers",
				"value": 100,
				"airdate": null,
				"category_id": 100,
				"game_id": null,
				"invalid_count": null
			}
		]
}`;
